Is Katherine from the Buffalo News?
Congratulations.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
>> Um, how would you describe your style of
play?
>> Oh, violent, fast, physical, and
religious.
>> Um, it says on our notes we got about
you that you were a team captain. What
was kind of your approach to that as a
leadership role?
>> Yo, lead by example. I ain't ask nobody
to do nothing that I ain't do myself.
[snorts]
>> Um, what were your conversations like
with the Bills leading up to the draft
and just kind of throughout the process?
Walk me through that.
>> Yeah, I had great conversations with
with all the the Bills, the Dline coach.
I talked to him a little bit, say he
like my style of play. Correct [snorts]
me on some things I can get better at.
Always trying to find a way to get
better. So, I got a great relationship
with him.
>> What was that like in, you know, you're
trying to make your best impression, but
you want those corrections as well so
you can improve. Just what was it like
balancing those feelings?
>> Yeah, I mean, you just got to keep you
got to keep it honest. So, you know,
coach coach No Ball, he coached the
best. You got Ed Oliver, Deion Walker, a
couple guys have been playing and doing
it at a high level. So, I mean, just to
be able to be on the phone with a coach
at the same time is a blessing. So, I
mean, I'm just taking it all in, being
grateful the opportunity.
>> Awesome. Thanks. And congrats again.
>> Thank you.
[snorts]
>> Hey, Zane. Elena Gettenberg with ESPN.
How are you?
>> What's good? How you doing? Good.
>> Good. Congratulations. Um, I was
curious, what has today been like for
you? Like, what has it been like waiting
to hear your name get called?
>> Yo, to be honest, man, I ain't no
waiting guy. You know what I'm saying? I
like to get stuff done, but you know,
that's a part of the process and I'm
just blessed and I'm grateful for the
opportunity. [snorts]
>> What was it like with with that in mind?
Like, what was it like when you did get
the phone call then?
>> Man, a s relief. You know what I'm
saying? Finally, pressure on your back.
No more guessing game. You know where
you're going.
>> Is there anything like you mentioned Ed
Oliver and um what do you know, I guess,
about the Bills? like what are you
excited about coming up here?
>> Yeah, man. The defensive line play, you
know what I'm saying? Y got some of the
best details in the league and I want to
solidify myself and try to learn from
them guys as much as I can.
>> Awesome. Thanks. Congratulations.
>> Thank you, [snorts]
>> Zane. Mookie Hawkins, W Sports 1080.
Congratulations.
>> How you doing? Thank you.
>> Now, Buffalo values interior disruption.
How do you see your skill set fitting
into this uh rotation?
>> Just doing the best I could do, man. I
mean, I'm fast off the ball and I'm
explosive and I'm strong at a point of
attack. So, trying to get [snorts] that
down with how they play ball up there
and learn as much as I can.
>> Do you view yourself more as a
penetration three tech or a versatile
interior piece, you know, that can move
around.
>> Yeah, I say versatile, but I'm I'm a
three tech at heart, but I play all
around in college, so I'm ready for
whatever. Now,
>> what have the coaches told you about
what your role would be early on? Uh,
>> they ain't tell me nothing. You know
what I'm saying? Just go in there, get
ready to work. You know what I'm saying?
Figure out the rest later.
Absolutely man. Appreciate your time and
congrats.
>> Thank you.
>> Hi Zayn. Sal Kapacio here WGR radio in
Buffalo. Congratulations.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. How you
doing?
>> I'm doing good. Who's the best athlete
in your family?
>> Me obviously.
>> Can you tell us a little bit about your
uh athletic family?
>> Yeah, so uh mom and dad both play
sports. Uh dad played college football.
My mom played every sport. uh track and
field volleyball, women's basketball in
high school. My older sister went to FIU
for women's basketball scholarship. My
my second older sister went UCF track
and field for shot play on scholarship.
Then the youngest just a baby and I'm
I'm the youngest of the family.
>> Um how has that athletic family and the
competitiveness kind of shaped you as a
football player?
>> Yeah, it always shaped me, man. So them
being older than me trying to compete
with them. Ever since I was a baby, I
used to lose, but I never I never
stopped and always tried to win. So
that's how I kind of keep my mentality.
whatever happens, just continue to work
for one foot from the other and get
better.
>> You know, you're going to be going
against probably primarily another
Nitney Lion right across the ball from
you and Conor McGovern who played center
uh you know at Penn State. I don't know
if you know Connor at all or anything
about him, but uh you guys will be in
the trenches together and practice a
lot.
>> Yo, I'm ready for it, man. I'm ready to
have fun. [snorts]
>> All right, congratulations. See you up
here.
>> Thank you.